Luigi Feitoza



luigihenrick@gmail.com



+5511982011319



linkedin.com/in/luigihenrick

Summary

Professional with over six years of experience as a developer. Mostly worked in the financial market delivering products for large-scale and distributed systems.

I've already worked for small and big companies as Itaú bank, XP Inc, and as a consultant for Original bank and Tecpay (point of sale system).

- Experience as a leader;
- Experience building new apps from scratch. Passing from solution architecture, backend systems, databases, infrastructure, cloud.
- Knowledge in design patterns.
- Best performance practices for code.
- Managing team, prioritizing new features and discovering technologies solutions.

Experience



Senior Software Engineer

adyou

Mar 2021 - Oct 2021 (8 months)

I've worked as a technical leader been responsible to create a new app from the scratch including all the architecture, infrastructure, build and release pipelines, communication between services thinking about performance, and cloud costs.

Also, I was in the middle between the business area and IT team helping to prioritize new features, search about new technologies and keep the team motivated.

Itaú

System Software Engineer

Itaú Unibanco

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021 (1 year 1 month)

I've worked on a new Itaú project called Íon, it's a new investment platform for customers to have more options and a better investing experience. All of this combined with all the security from one of the biggest banks of Latin America. Technologies used: dotnet core; C#, WebAPIs, AWS cloud; Kotlin; Android; GIT.

XPIInc.

Software Developer

XP Inc.

Nov 2018 - Nov 2019 (1 year 1 month)

I've developed backend systems to structured products to turn scalable and reach more customers. Between the main deliveries are send proposals of options to customer mobile phone, create proposals templates and show these templates on customer positions.

Technologies used: Microservices architecture; WebAPIs; Message Queues; Azure DevOps; Service Fabric; .NET Core; C#; AngularJS; Windows Communication Foundation (WCF); SQL Server; Oracle.

Junior Software Developer

Beyond Soluções

Feb 2018 - Nov 2018 (10 months)

I have worked as a consultant in the biggest Latin America independent brokerage at the team that is responsible for developing the new customer platform of structured notes products and other important deliveries like orders by push notification and a new backend architecture to support a huge number of requests.

Main technologies used: Microservices architecture; CQRS; WebAPIs; Visual Studio Team Services (Azure DevOps); Continuous Integration; C#; Oracle; SQL Server; Agile Methodologies (Scrum); Git.

Web Developer Internship

TurnIT

Mar 2017 - Feb 2018 (1 year)

I've participated in all steps of web solutions since prospecting clients until analysis and developing systems for financial companies like Banco Original, TecPay, Lotus Investments, Moka Invest, and another's.

Technologies used: C#, ASP.NET MVC 4/5, SQL Server 2014, HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS3, Bootstrap 3, code versioning in Git/Bitbucket.

IT Support Technician

Nov 2015 - Mar 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Responsible for creating an android application and web services to helps the customer attendance. Implementation of several improvements in your network infrastructure including a creation of a VoIP server and implementation of IP phones.

Education

Faculdade de Tecnologia de São Paulo

System Analysis and Development, Information Technology 2015 - 2019

★ Universidade Cidade de São Paulo

Certificate in IT, Information Technology 2014 - 2015

Licenses & Certifications



★ Certificate in IT - Universidade Cidade de São Paulo

Skills

C# • .NET Core • Azure DevOps • Git • Agile Methodologies • Cloud Applications • Microservices Message Queue
REST APIs
SQL